https://www.antiquelightingcompany.com/privacy-policy/

Information about our Organisation and Website Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of The Exeter Antique Lighting Company. Our privacy policy covers The Exeter Antique Lighting Company and its website:Address: The Exeter Antique Lighting Company 43 The Quay Exeter EX2 4AN United KingdomShowroom: +44(0)1392 433604 Mobile: +44(0)7702 969438 email: julian@antiquelightingcompany.com Web Site: www.antiquelightingcompany.comProviding Visitors with Anonymous Access You can access our Website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.The services and links of our Web site Our Website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.Automatic Collection of Information The Exeter Antique Lighting Company  cookies are only used to identify the customer, not to identify any specific customer traits. These cookies do not store any sensitive data. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do automatically log user’s IP address and session information such as the duration of the visit and the type of browser used. This is recognised by the web server and is only used for system administration and to provide statistics which the business uses to evaluate use of the site.Data Collection and Purpose Specification We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than the specific services such as feedback forms. If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected.Children’s Privacy We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection of the child’s personal data.Disclosure and Visitor Choice We do not disclose your personal data to other organisations.Confidentiality / Security We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:    unauthorised access    improper use or disclosure    unauthorised modification    unlawful destruction or accidental lossAll our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law, other regulation or for funding purposes.Access to the personal data we may hold about you You can ask us whether we are keeping personal data about you upon request, which you can indicate by:Sending an emailCalling this telephone number Showroom: +44(0)1392 433604 Mobile: +44(0)7702 969438We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week – although we will before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information at a charge of £10. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified or amended. We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.Privacy Compliance Our privacy policy is compliant with the United Kingdom’s Data Protection Act 1998. In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the Data Protection Act, we are subject to an Independent Data Protection Authority: Information Commissioner www.dataprotection.gov.uk Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, UKPrivacy Support If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:Address: The Exeter Antique Lighting Company 43 The Quay ExeterEX2 4AN United KingdomShowroom: +44(0)1392 433604 Mobile: +44(0)7702 969438 email: julian@antiquelightingcompany.com Web Site: www.antiquelightingcompany.comIf you are not satisfied with our response to your concern you may wish to contact Information Commissioner (http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/).CategoriesAntique Ceiling LightsAntique Ceiling Lights, Pairs and RunsAntique Holophane Pendant LightsAntique Small Ceiling Pendant LightsAntique Rise And Fall LightsArt Nouveau/Arts & CraftsArt DecoAntique Close Fitting Ceiling LightsAntique Plafonnier / Hanging Bowl Ceiling LightsAntique Table LampsAntique Wall LightsAntique Crystal ChandeliersAntique LanternsAntique Library Lights/ Standard LightsAntique French Pate de Verre LightsAntique CandlesticksAntique Industrial Style Lights – Singles, PairsReproduction Crystal ChandeliersVintage Edison style light bulbsLighting Spares and AccessoriesCeiling Hooks / GalleriesBulb Holders / CableReproduction ShadesAntique ShadesMiscellaneous PartsHomeAbout UsServicesContactVisit UsPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsCookie PolicySite Map Copyright © Exeter Antique Lighting Company 2020. All Rights Reserved.
